Don't Iisten to her.
Go to the movie theater.
- Take me home now.
- Movie theater.
(Sheldon:)Okay, everybody, calm down.
There is a simple solution here.
(Sheldon:)Raj, take me to the train store...
(Sheldon:)...and then I don't care
what you people do.
(Amy:)How was your shower?
(Leonard:)Good, good.
(Leonard:)Just out of curiosity,
what time do you usually go to bed?
(Amy:)Oh, I'm up all night.
I'm like a possum.
(Amy:)Boy, you were not liked in high school,
were you?
- Not really. Is that my yearbook?
- Mm-hm.
"Dear Leonard,
you're really good at science.
(Amy:)Maybe one day you'll come up
with a cure for being a dork."
(Leonard:)It wasn't spray-painting
a lightning boIt on my briefcase.
(Leonard:)- I can tell you that.
- If it makes you feel any better...
(Amy:)...the only person who signed
my yearbook was my mother.
(Leonard:)Aw.
"Dear Amy, seIf-respect and a hymen are
better than friends and fun. Love, Mom."